ILR School Photographs /4117 P
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Photographs
1945-1996
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/4117 P
6.78 cubic feet
7.4 linear ft.
Photographs.
Images include alumni, visitors, departments, awards, events, and faculty members
7926498
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, December 18, 2012
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, September 30, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /4206 P: ILR School Martin P. Catherwood Library Photographs /4264 P: ILR School Communications Department Photographs /4275 P: ILR School Conference Center Group Photographs from Conferences /4280 P: ILR School Ives Hallway Portrait Gallery Photographs /4283 P: ILR School Extension Division (Buffalo, N.Y.) Photographs /4289 P: ILR School Alumni Affairs and Development Photographs 6038 P: Photographs Archival Collection
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.
7926498
- Faculty Group - ILR (Box 1, Folder 1)
  Scope and Contents
  12 photographs
- Alumni and others (Box 1, Folder 2)
  2 photographs
- Alumni files (Box 1, Folder 3)
  5 photographs
- Aboud, Grace & Anton (Box 1, Folder 4)
  7 photographs
- Aiges, Stan - 1958 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Alian, LaVerne Rolle - 1974 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  1 photograph
- Alloway, Richard - 1950 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Alpern, Jerry - 1949 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  4 photographs
- Ammond, Harold - 1951 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Argyis, Chris (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Asher, William (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Behnke, Carl (Box 1, Folder 12)
  10 photographs
- Berenblum, Marvin - 1988 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Binstock, Stu - 1975 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Bluestein, Robert - 1967 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Brizel, Mike - 1977 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Chabon, Robert (Box 1, Folder 17)
  2 photograph
- Colosi, Tom - 1958 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  3 photographs
- Peter Cusak (Box 1, Folder 19)
  13 photographs
- Donahue, Humphrey (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Dorf, Gerald - 1957 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Douglas, Bob - 1973 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Downey, Tom - 1970 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Duzak, Thomas - 1969 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Edwards, Harry (Judge) - 1962 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Esman, Oliver - 1974 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  1 photographs
- Fanning, John (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Fasser, Paul - 1951 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Finch, Dave -1973 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Fincher, Dick - 1973 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Flamm, Arthur (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Flynn, Joseph - 1947 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Foss, Linda (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Fowler, George - 1948 (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Gabor, Marc - 1976 (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Galenson, Walter (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Goldstein, Richard - 1949 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  8 photographs
- Golodner, Jack - 1953 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Green, Thomas - 1963 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Greenbaum, Marcia - 1962 (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Greenspan, Joan - 1964 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  17 photographs
- Grossman, Mark - 1965 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Grosso, James (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Hack, Anne - 1981 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Hardin, Frances - 1975 (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Hawryluk, Ted - 1949 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Hayes, Robert - 1973 (Box 1, Folder 47)
- Helsby, Robert (Box 1, Folder 48)
- Higgins, John - 1970 (Box 1, Folder 49)
- Hodes, Joel - 1968 (Box 1, Folder 50)
- Hodes, Nancy - 1968 (Box 1, Folder 51)
- Hoffman, Peter - 1964 (Box 1, Folder 52)
- Hollander, Scott - 1973 (Box 1, Folder 53)
- Humphrey, Anne - 1973 (Box 1, Folder 54)
- Jachter, Rose (Box 1, Folder 55)
- Jacobson, Carolyn - 1972 (Box 1, Folder 56)
- Jedel, Michael Jay (Box 1, Folder 57)
- Jensen, Eric - 1951 (Box 1, Folder 58)
- Kilberg, William - 1966 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  6 photographs
- Kheel, Ted (Box 1, Folder 60)
- Kobrin, Raphael (Box 1, Folder 61)
- Kolko, Mort - 1955 (Box 1, Folder 62)
- Kramer, Saul - 1954 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  11 photographs
- Linnick, Stuart - 1959 (Box 1, Folder 64)
- Mahon, John (Box 1, Folder 65)
- Marchigrane, Albert - 1951 (Box 1, Folder 66)
- McCall, Morgan - 1974 (Box 1, Folder 67)
- McCarthy, Nancy (Box 1, Folder 68)
- McIntyre, Thomas (Box 1, Folder 69)
- McKay, Joseph - 1961 (Box 1, Folder 70)
- McKersie (Box 1, Folder 71)
- Meachem, Norma - 1974 (Box 1, Folder 72)
- Meyer, Charles (Box 1, Folder 73)
- Miller, David - 1971 (Box 1, Folder 74)
- Miserendino, Rich - 1975 (Box 1, Folder 75)
- Mitrani, Robert - 1951 (Box 1, Folder 76)
- Moffett, Ken (Box 1, Folder 77)
- Profile - Eliz Moore - Spring 1986 (Box 1, Folder 78)
- Nedd, Albert (Box 1, Folder 79)
- Nevin, Tom (Box 1, Folder 80)
- Newman, Jay - 1971 (Box 1, Folder 81)
- Oles, Carl - 1955 (Box 1, Folder 82)
- Owens, Debra (Box 1, Folder 83)
- Parvin, Landon (Box 1, Folder 84)
- Lynn Paltrow - 1979 (Box 1, Folder 85)
- Pereles, Ed (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Phillips, Bill (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Ploscowe, Stephen - 1962 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Rodgers, Don - 1952 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Rosenthal, Don - 1972 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Rothfeld, Myra (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Paul Salvatore - 1981 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Vicki Saporta - 1974 (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Schaefer, Dick (Box 2, Folder 9)
  9 photographs
- Dick Schaap (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Schappi, John - 1951 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Seidenberg, Sue (Box 2, Folder 12)
- Sheinkman, Jack - 1949 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Shephard, Ira - 1968 (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Siegel, Rita - 1969 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Sudenberg, Jacob (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Torgman, David (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Truesdale, John - NLRB -- 1948 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- Turley, Tom - 1975 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Wachter, Michael L. (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Alan Weitzman - 1970 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Robin Wolaner - 1975 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Yager, Paul - 1949 (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Younger, Judith - 1954 (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Bob Zelmick - 1961 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Misc. Alumni Activities - Photos (Box 2, Folder 26)
  46 photographs
- Abel, I.W. (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Anderson, Warren (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Boyer, Ernest (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Brennan, Peter (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Brock Secretary of Labor (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Cook, Constance (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Counts, Curtis (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Davis, Leon (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Hoffa, James (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Gavdion, Donald (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Hodgson, James (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Hunter, Lawrence (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Javitts, Sen. Jacob (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Johnston, Robert (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Kheel, Ted (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Kirkland, Lane (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Krupsak, Mary Ann (Lt. Gov. New York State) (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Levy, Norman (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Lundine, Lt. Gov. Stan (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Miller, Marvin (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Netter, Richard (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Raskin, Abe (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Rhodes, Pres. Frank H.T. (Box 2, Folder 49)
- Rockefeller, Nelson (Box 2, Folder 50)
- Rosenberg, B. (Box 2, Folder 51)
- Shafer, Dick (Box 2, Folder 52)
- Shanker, Albert (President-AFT) (Box 2, Folder 53)
- Smith, Roger (GM) (Box 2, Folder 54)
- Smithers, R. Brinkley (Box 2, Folder 55)
- Steingut, Stanley (Box 2, Folder 56)
- Van Arsdale, Harry -- ILR 50th Anniv. (Box 2, Folder 57)
- Weisburger, June (Box 2, Folder 58)
- Whitfield, Dennis (Box 2, Folder 59)
- Wyatt, Addie (Box 2, Folder 60)
- Alumni Assoc. Bd. of Directors (Box 2, Folder 61)
- Alpern Fellow (Box 2, Folder 62)
- Audio-visual Center (Box 2, Folder 63)
- Career Center (Box 2, Folder 64)
- Catherwood Library (Box 3, Folder 1)
  26
- Catherwood Library (2) (Box 3, Folder 2)
  26 photographs
- Catherwood Library (3) (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Catherwood Library - Recent - 1987 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Contacts 1989 Library Shoot (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Center for Advanced Human Resource Studies (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Classroom Shots (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Collective Bargaining Institute Photos 3/1987 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  10 photographs; 20 slides
- Computers & Students (Box 3, Folder 9)
  14 photographs
- Conferences (Box 3, Folder 10)
  20 photographs
- Extension Faculty (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Field Study (Box 3, Folder 12)
  19 photographs
- 50th Anniv./Lack, Cleary, Cole, Construction (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Fortieth Anniversary (Box 3, Folder 14)
  27 photographs
- 40th Anniv. (Box 3, Folder 15)
  32 photographs
- Founders Course Labor Relations in Professional Employment (Doherty), Spr. 1978 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Governor Dewey, Dedication of School, 1945 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Groat Awards, 1981, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Groat Pictures 1983 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  28 photographs
- Groat 1984 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Groat 1985 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Groat 1986 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Groat Award 1990 (Box 3, Folder 23)
- IBM Computers 1984 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Groat Breakfast [1996] (David Lubarsky, Photographer) (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Historical Photos (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Homecoming 1996 (Box 3, Folder 27)
- ILR Associates: Corning Glass - 10/1984 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- ILR Council (Box 3, Folder 29)
  21 photographs
- ILR Faculty (Box 3, Folder 30)
- ILR Film 1984 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Labor Day Convocation (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Labor Leaders (Box 4, Folder 3)
- NLRB Conference - Fall 1984 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- NYS AFL-CIO 1980 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  15 photographs
- Past ILR Deans (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Pension Conference -- May 1981 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- PEWS (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Publications ILR Press (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Reunion 1986 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Reunion 1987 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Reunion 1988 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Reunion 1990 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Students - Pre 1971 (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Students 1971 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  18 photographs
- 25th Anniversary Dinner - NYC (Box 4, Folder 16)
- 25th Anniv. Dinner - NYC (2) (Box 4, Folder 17)
- 25th Anniversary Dinner - Ithaca (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Visiting Practitioners (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Contacts: 40th Anniv. (Box 4, Folder 20)
- CBI Contacts - 5/11/1987 (New Borneo, Claude Levet) (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Contacts: Don Milici 1976 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Contacts: pre-1978 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- 1978 - Russ Hamilton (Box 4, Folder 24)
- ILR Faculty - Emeritus (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Contacts - Chris Powers - 1980 -- Faculty and Staff (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Contacts - Jon Crispin -- 2/1984 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- ILR Presidents - Boone Pickens -- 4/10/1986 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Press, Mr. Reid, Review Office -- 1981 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- School Relations Contacts - Charlie Harrington -- 2/4/1987 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- Contacts - Harrington -- 9/1988 (Box 5, Folder 4)
- Contacts -- Harrington -- 3/1986 (Box 5, Folder 5)
- Collages, etc. Harrington -- 6/1989 -- From Admissions (Box 5, Folder 6)
- Collages, etc. Harrington -- 1/1989 (2) (Box 5, Folder 7)
  36 slides
- Visiting Professors (Box 5, Folder 8)
- Abowd, John (Box 5, Folder 9)
- Aldrich, Howard (Box 5, Folder 10)
- Aronson, Robert (Box 5, Folder 11)
- Ash, Karin (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Bacharach, Samuel (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Bailey, Holly (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Barley, Stephen (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Benson, Frances (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Bishop, John (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Blumen, Isador (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Boudreau, John (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Boyer, George (Box 5, Folder 20)
  empty
- Bretz, Robert (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Briggs, Vernon (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Broderick, Renae (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Brooks, George (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Brophy, Jackie (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Bruyere, Susanne (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Burton, John (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Butler, Richard (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Calvert, George (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Campbell, Ralph (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Chapman, David (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Clark, Gardner (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Coghill, Maryann (Box 5, Folder 33)
- Cook, Alice (Box 5, Folder 34)
  16 photographs
- Craypo, Charles (Box 5, Folder 35)
- Cullen, Donald (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Cullen, Mary (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Daniel, Cletus (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Dankert, Philip R. (Box 5, Folder 39)
- DeCotiis, Thomas A. (Box 5, Folder 40)
  newspaper clipping
- Delacruz, Gregory (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Demarchi, Gerard A. (Box 5, Folder 42)
  no photos
- Dennis, Rodney (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Devault, Ileen (Box 5, Folder 44)
  news clipping with picture
- Dietrich, Donald (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Doherty, Robert (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Donovan, Ronald (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Drotning, John (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Dyer, Lee (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Eastman, David (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Eder, Robert (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Ehrenberg, Ronald (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Emerson, Eleanor (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Farley, Jennie (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Ferguson, Robert (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Fields, Gary (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Finn, Melvin (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Foltman, Felician (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Fowler, William (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Fowler, William (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Francis, Ivor (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Frank, William (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Freeman, Virginia (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Gagala, Kenneth (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Galenson, Walter (Box 6, Folder 12)
- Gamm, Sara (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Gellerman, Bill (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Gerhart, Barry (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Ghosh, Rita (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Gilcher, Kay (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Gold, Charlotte (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Gold, Michael (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Gonzalez, Eddie (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Gordon, Jerry (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Gramm, Cynthia (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Grant, Irene (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Gray, Lois (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Grolli, Bill (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Gross, James (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Gruenfeld, Elaine (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Gruenfeld, Leopold (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Hadi, Ali (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Hamlin, Clark (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Hammer, Tove (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Hanslowe, Kurt (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Harrel, Shirley (Box 6, Folder 33)
  1 photograph; news clippings
- Harper, Shirley (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Harrison, David L. (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Herson, Thomas (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Hildebrand, George (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Hodges, Wayne (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Holcomb, William B. (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Hopkins, Robert (Box 6, Folder 40)
- House, Ronald (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Huber, Vandra (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Hurd, Richard (Box 6, Folder 43)
  news clipping
- Hutchens, Robert M. (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Huttar, James (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Jakubson, George (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Jensen, Vernon (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Judge, Timothy (Box 7, Folder 1)
- Julian, Robert (Box 7, Folder 2)
- Kane, Donald (Box 7, Folder 3)
- Katz, Harry (Box 7, Folder 4)
- Kaufman, Jacob J. (Box 7, Folder 5)
- Kheel, Ted (Box 7, Folder 6)
- Keeran, Roger (Box 7, Folder 7)
- Keggi, John (Box 7, Folder 8)
- Kelly, Matthew A. (Box 7, Folder 9)
- Kennedy, Marian (Box 7, Folder 10)
- Kennedy, Martin (Box 7, Folder 11)
- Kirmeyer, Sandra (Box 7, Folder 12)
- Kochan, Tom (Box 7, Folder 13)
- Konvitz, Milton (Box 7, Folder 14)
- Konvitz (Box 7, Folder 15)
  34
- Korman, Gurd, A. (Box 7, Folder 16)
- Lall, Betty (Box 7, Folder 17)
- Lampman, Robert (Box 7, Folder 18)
- Landsberger, Henry (Box 7, Folder 19)
- Law, Gordon (Box 7, Folder 20)
- Lawler, Edward (Box 7, Folder 21)
- Lazes, Peter (Box 7, Folder 22)
- Levine, Lou (Box 7, Folder 23)
- Levy, Jonathon (Box 7, Folder 24)
- Lieberwitz, Risa (Box 7, Folder 25)
- Lindsley, Theodore (Box 7, Folder 26)
- Lipsky, David (Box 7, Folder 27)
  34 photographs
- Macintyre, Duncan (Box 7, Folder 28)
- Martin, Ann (Box 7, Folder 29)
- McCarthy, Phil (Box 7, Folder 30)
- McConnel, John (Box 7, Folder 31)
- McCulloch, Frank W. (Box 7, Folder 32)
  text
- McKelvey, Jean (Box 7, Folder 33)
  25 photographs
- McKelvey, Jean (Box 7, Folder 34)
- McKelvey, Jean (Box 7, Folder 35)
- Director Bernie Naas Portrait (Box 8)
  - Bernie Naas (Box 8, Folder 1)
    framed photograph
- Director Shirley Harper Portrait (Box 9)
  - Shirley Harper (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Director Gormly Miller Portrait (Box 10)
  - Gormly Miller (Box 10, Folder 1)
- Misc. student photographs (Box 11, Folder 1)
  removed from drawer 8 of Mapcase - oversize photographs (5)
- McKersie, Robert (Box 12, Folder 1)
- McKersie, Robert (Box 12, Folder 2)
- McPherson, Jim (Box 12, Folder 3)
- Mesics, Emil (Box 12, Folder 4)
- Milkovich, George (Box 12, Folder 5)
- Miller, Frank (Box 12, Folder 6)
  9 photographs; news clippings
- Miller, J. Gormly (Box 12, Folder 7)
- Miller, Mona (Box 12, Folder 8)
- Mishel, Larry (Box 12, Folder 9)
- Mitchell, Olivia (Box 12, Folder 10)
- Moore, Alice (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Moore, David (Box 12, Folder 12)
- Morris, Charles (Box 12, Folder 13)
- Morris, James O. (Box 12, Folder 14)
- Muller, Susan J. (Box 12, Folder 15)
- Nash, Al (Box 12, Folder 16)
- Nedd, Albert (Box 12, Folder 17)
- Nelson, Ann (Box 12, Folder 18)
- Newman, Harold (Box 12, Folder 19)
- Neufeld, Maurice (Box 12, Folder 20)
- Neufeld, Maurice (cont.) (Box 12, Folder 21)
- Pivetz, Dick (Box 12, Folder 22)
- Prago, Al (Box 12, Folder 23)
  no photographs
- Pucick, Vladimir (Box 12, Folder 24)
  was in bx7ff56a -- 1 photograph
- Rachlin, Marjorie (Box 12, Folder 25)
- Raimon, Robert I. (Box 13, Folder 1)
- Rhemus, Charles (Box 13, Folder 2)
- Reid, Michael (Box 13, Folder 3)
- Risley, Robert (Box 13, Folder 4)
- Rosen, Ned (Box 13, Folder 5)
- Ross, Philip (Box 13, Folder 6)
- Rynes, Sara (Box 13, Folder 7)
- Salvatore (Box 13, Folder 8)
  Text and news clippings with pictures
- Salvatore, Nicholas (Box 13, Folder 9)
- Seeber, Ronald (Box 13, Folder 10)
- Shady, Jeanette P. (Box 13, Folder 11)
- Slavick, Fred (Box 13, Folder 12)
- Sonnenstuhl, William (Box 13, Folder 13)
- Simpson, Steve (Box 13, Folder 14)
- Smith, Alpheus (Box 13, Folder 15)
- Smith, Arthur (Box 13, Folder 16)
- Smith, Robert (Box 13, Folder 17)
  7 photographs; news clippings
- Sniezek, Janet (Box 13, Folder 18)
  news clippings with pictures
- SRB, Jo (Box 13, Folder 19)
- Stern, Robert (Box 13, Folder 20)
- Stotz, David (Box 13, Folder 21)
- Strassberg, Richard (Box 13, Folder 22)
- Strausser, Pamela (Box 13, Folder 23)
- Suci, Nan (Box 13, Folder 24)
- Stolkov, Vladimir (Box 13, Folder 25)
- Tolbert, Pamela (Box 13, Folder 26)
- Tolles, Arnold (Box 13, Folder 27)
- Student activities photos (Box 14, Folder 18)
- Trice, Harrison (Box 14, Folder 1)
- Velleman, Paul (Box 14, Folder 2)
- Wasmuth, William (Box 14, Folder 3)
- Wertheimer, Barbara (Box 14, Folder 4)
- Whyte, William (Box 14, Folder 5)
  15 black and white photographs and text
- Wilcox, Duane (Box 14, Folder 6)
- Williams, Larry (Box 14, Folder 7)
  15 photographs; news clippings
- Windmuller, John (Box 14, Folder 8)
- Wolf, William (Box 14, Folder 9)
- Woodruff, Tom (Box 14, Folder 10)
- Yaffe, Byron (Box 14, Folder 11)
- Zimmerman, Don (Box 14, Folder 12)
- Grant, Alice (Box 14, Folder 13)
  8 photographs; 1 slide
- NYSSILR Informational slideshow, ca. 1980s - (Box 14, Folder 14)
  19 slides, accompanying cassette in media case, now box 15
- ILR informational slideshow 1980's (cont.) (Box 14, Folder 15)
  19 slides
- ILR informational slideshow 1980's (Box 14, Folder 16)
  18 slides
- ILR informational slideshow 1980's (Box 14, Folder 17)
- NYSSILR Informational slideshow, ca. 1980s (Box 15, Folder 1)
  cassette accompanies papers in box 14, ff14
- Images digitized from the collection. (Box 16)